[
    {
        "question": "Who am I?",
        "choice1": "Noob Coder",
        "choice2": "Tech_Sammy",
        "choice3": "Samuel",
        "choice4": "Merko kya pata / idk and idc",
        "answer": 1
    },
    {
        "question": "What comes to your mind when you hear tech_sammy?",
        "choice1": "Noob Coder",
        "choice2": "Noobda hai sala",
        "choice3": "Learner,like me(you)...",
        "choice4": "Merko kya pata / idk and idc",
        "answer": 2
    },
    {
        "question": "Is tech_sammy an introvert?",
        "choice1": "No",
        "choice2": "Darpoke hai sala",
        "choice3": "Yessssssssssssss!",
        "choice4": "Merko kya pata / idk and idc",
        "answer": 2
    },
    {
        "question": "What is tech_sammy most scared of?",
        "choice1": "Grills",
        "choice2": "Blackholes",
        "choice3": "Time Travel",
        "choice4": "Merko kya pata / idk and idc",
        "answer": 1
    },
    {
        "question": "Does Sammy have girlfriend?",
        "choice1": "Yup",
        "choice2": "He prefers to be alone",
        "choice3": "Nope",
        "choice4": "Merko kya pata / idk and idc",
        "answer": 2
    },
    {
        "question": "IS it OK to ask him if he's Single?",
        "choice1": "No",
        "choice2": "Yes!",
        "choice3": "Yup!But who would even ask such a looser ",
        "choice4": "Merko kya pata / idk and idc",
        "answer": 3
    },
    {
        "question": "Who is Sammy's Best Friend?",
        "choice1": "Someone I don't know.",
        "choice2": "Games",
        "choice3": "Coding/Technology",
        "choice4": "Merko kya pata / idk and idc",
        "answer": 4
    },
    {
        "question": "Where does Sammy spend most of his time?",
        "choice1": "Studies / Coding",
        "choice2": "Games",
        "choice3": "Chatting/Meeting his friends",
        "choice4": "Merko kya pata / idk and idc",
        "answer": 4
    },
    {
        "question": "Can Sammy cross 1k followers till next month?",
        "choice1": "Impossible",
        "choice2": "Possible",
        "choice3": "Itni Jaldi bhi kya hai..",
        "choice4": "Merko kya pata / idk and idc",
        "answer": 3
    },
    {
        "question": "Can Sammy make it to Google?",
        "choice1": "No",
        "choice2": "Tumse na ho payega :( ",
        "choice3": "Yes!",
        "choice4": "Merko kya pata / idk and idc",
        "answer": 2
    }
]